learnandmaster.com 2016-02-05

# Legacy Learning Systems Privacy Policy | Guitar, Piano, Drums, Painting, Photography, Ballroom Dance DVD Instruction

* * *

## Privacy Policy

**Legacy Learning Systems Inc. Privacy Policy**

Legacy Learning Systems, Inc. (“Legacy Learning Systems”) takes your privacy seriously and this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) uses and protects any information that you give Legacy Learning Systems, Inc. when you use this website.

Legacy Learning Systems is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Policy.

This Policy applies to all of the products and services offered through LearnandMaster.com. Legacy Learning Systems may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically to ensure that you are in agreement with any changes.

**Notice.**  
Legacy Learning Systems is committed to clearly and readily disclosing its data collection practices so that you can make informed decisions about your activities on LearnandMaster.com.

**Choice.**  
Legacy Learning Systems provides you with a choice to participate in its data collection activities.

**Access.**  
Legacy Learning Systems provides you with the opportunity to review, modify, and delete any personally identifiable information that you have previously provided. To review the information we have for you, or to have us delete any of your information, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, please contact us:  
Write: Legacy Learning Systems, 2510 Franklin Pike, Second Floor, Nashville, TN 37204  
Email: [service@leglearn.com](mailto:service@leglearn.com)  
Phone: 866-683-6027

**Security.**  
Legacy Learning Systems has taken proactive measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of data that it collects and stores. Legacy Learning Systems’ network infrastructure utilizes leading technology, including Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software which encrypts information, to protect data at each point of transfer. Legacy Learning Systems utilizes up to date physical security procedures to limit access to the data so that any access is consistent with this Policy. Legacy Learning Systems transmits your entire credit card number to Authorize.Net during order processing.

**Information Collected.**  
So that we can provide the best possible service and improve our customer experience, Legacy Learning Systems may collect the following information:

  * Customer details you provide us, including first and last name, email address (at field level), shipping and billing address, phone number, company name.
  * Payment information may also be collected, where necessary, through our secure checkout process.
  * Cookies. When you visit LearnandMaster.com, we may send one or more cookies (small file containing characters which identify your browser). Most browsers are set to accept cookies but you can modify your browser’s settings to reject or delete cookies from some or all websites, including LearnandMaster.com.

**User Communications.** If you send an email or other communication to Legacy Learning Systems, we may retain those communications and the personal information you provide in order to fulfill your request of us. We will not use your return email addresses for any other use without your consent.

**Affiliated Web Sites.** Legacy Learning Systems may offer products and services in connection with third-party websites. Personally identifiable information that you provide to third-party websites may be sent to Legacy Learning Systems. Legacy Learning Systems processes such personally identifiable information in accordance with this Policy. The third-party websites may have different privacy practices and you should read their privacy policies before giving them your personal information.

**Links.** Legacy Learning Systems may present links in a format that tracks whether these links have been followed. This information is used internally to improve the quality of Legacy Learning Systems’ products, services, and this website by tracking user trends.

**Third-Party Web Sites.** This Policy only applies to this website and any other website owned and operated by Legacy Learning Systems. Please be aware that Legacy Learning Systems is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other websites and does not exercise control over third-party websites displayed as links anywhere on this website. These third-party websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, or solicit personally identifiable information from you. In certain instances, if you affirmatively click through to access sponsored content or materials at sponsored websites, or affirmatively click through on a link/ad, that user's information may be shared with the sponsor.

**Advertising.** Legacy Learning Systems works with third-party partners, including Google, who automatically collect anonymous, non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our websites. This information is collected using cookies.

Cookies are small amounts of data that are stored on your computer within your browser. They are placed on your computer via a web server when you visit our site. Cookies are safe for your computer or device and are only used to report information about your activity on our website. We never use cookies to save passwords, credit card numbers or any other confidential information. With these third-party partner tools, such as Google Analytics and Google Adwords, we receive data that allows us to provide you with improved services and site experiences. The anonymous information is used to analyze general patterns, trends and demographics of vistors visiting our website.

Information gathered may include, but is not limited to, age, gender, IP address, site navigation patterns, frequency of visits, and interests. Legacy Learning Systems may use this information to inform, optimize and serve advertisements (banners, text ads, and links) on third-party websites. This means we may create targeted advertisements for display on other websites for Legacy Learning Systems products and services that are tailored to fit your interests. We will never run interest-based advertising campaigns that collect or disperse confidential information, such as email addresses, telephone numbers, and credit card numbers. 

If you wish to adjust your [Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) and [ advertising settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjs3rCXFJUAom--99bqgmrmSWv2rAWTmIpCHtquWLxkhKhP91Ap2qcx59F7vkCR5culipVSmaa2h62J7nAGwyHpwKgQhSVaDvy57Li8UGFLTKJEt-G_pwuf-C8ShpLL13wnhNoYQkFxbpbqBczw5UIhHdtXIe8FtlPdX1t5aqQm33JMt4dWqLQSwHA7JtDmQF3sYBs_q80uRpxlcotdNh-LBpxrFzEYCUeCkt7Uf0h7LNJ3kbjRA_4UFe2fZ1lOdfuTBk6rI3v6BtXQgb-xJcEF-w4TnQ), please see Google's currently available opt-outs for the web by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). Alternatively users may opt out of third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**How Legacy Learning Systems Uses Your Information.**  
You will occasionally receive emails containing information on products, services, special offers, contests, promotions, or newsletters. Legacy Learning Systems will always provide you with a mechanism to opt-out from receiving these types of communications within the communication itself.

Legacy Learning Systems may disclose certain details of your personally identifiable information to third-party service providers in order to fulfill your order. These third-party service providers have agreed to use your personally identifiable information only to fulfill your order and to keep it secure and confidential. Legacy Learning Systems may share aggregate information, such as usage and demographic data, with third parties. Aggregate information does not include personally identifiable information.

Legacy Learning Systems may use your data for customer service purposes, such as contacting customers who have not checked out, to follow up on abandoned shopping carts or to see if there was a problem with their use of the site.

Legacy Learning Systems is the sole owner of all information collected on this website.  
Legacy Learning Systems will not sell, share, or rent this information to any third parties, except as set forth in this Policy.  
Legacy Learning Systems reserves the right to disclose any information collected at this website if required by law or valid order of a court or other governmental authority.

Please note, if you decide not to receive marketing emails from Legacy Learning Systems, you may still receive 'Transactional' email messages regarding your order (i.e., order confirmation, shipping information, customer service notifications, abandoned shopping cart reminders, etc.). You can easily opt out of all email communications from us by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of all email messages. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us at [support@leglearn.com](mailto:support@leglearn.com).

**Controlling your personal information.**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to opt-out of any communication from Legacy Learning Systems.
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing or emailing us at the contact information listed above.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be inaccurate.

**Your California Privacy Rights.**  
Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits those customers that are California residents to request information about how Legacy Learning Systems discloses certain categories of personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. California residents may also request that Legacy Learning Systems not share your personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct marketing use. Except as set out in this Policy, Legacy Learning Systems does not presently share personally identifiable information with any third parties.

**Contact Information.**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding this Policy, please contact Legacy Learning Systems:   
Phone: 866-683-6027   
Email: [service@legacyinstruction.com](mailto:service@legacyinstruction.com)  
Postal Address: 2510 Franklin Pike, Second Floor, Nashville, TN 37204   
Web site URL: [www.learnandmaster.com](http://www.learnandmaster.com/)

EFFECTIVE DATE: July 13, 2011  
LAST UPDATE: February 5, 2014
